[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
I thought I'd never
feel this way about anyone again in my life...
but this kid is the exception.
Whenever I'm with this one,
I'm over the moon.
I feel really comfortable.
I want us to be together...
Are you hitting on me?
Yes, just now realizing that?
[Two weeks later]
- Jam.
- Oh!
Mr. Sarm.
What is it?
Nothing.
I'm here to see you.
Why are you here to see me?
♫Why am I here?♫
♫If I didn't love you, I wouldn't be here♫
Confused?
Ever heard of it?
Never heard of the song.
It is probably before my time.
Why are you here, really?
Why do you not go back to your place?
It's you
who is my home.
Can I borrow the chair?
What are you doing?
- Boo!
- Whoa!
Why did you trick me?
Eh?
How did I trick you, exactly?
You were not sleeping.
I was, actually.
Well,
the moment I sat down
and put my head on the table,
I fell right asleep.
Then I woke up because I got hungry.
- Is this for me?
- Hey.
No, it is not yours.
Not yours.
What?
It is yours.
Thank you.
Alright.
Since you made it, I have to serve it to you, too.
Actually, it was great back at the beach.
Which moment?
Was it when you got talked into climbing the coconut tree
and got stuck?
Hey.
Listen.
Can you not rub it in so much?
I get embarrassed too, you know.
It wasn't just me, though.
You
sang a duet with me
and got a perfect score at karaoke, no?
Who else, if not you?
I was there for six whole months,
but if any of it truly meant something...
it was those last two weeks.
How so, may I ask?
It's like...
I met someone...
who made my heart race.
Obviously.
You were being hunted down
and on the run,
so it was only natural for your heart to be racing.
Right?
Mm.
And...
you're not scared of ghosts when you're here alone?
I am not, actually.
I'm a ghost, too, you know?
Are you scared of me?
- Boo!
- Whoa!
Someone like you?
Even a shaman could not handle you.
You...
Despite being this tiny,
you're full of attitude, aren't you?
Even a shaman couldn't handle me,
but...
you...
you can.
When will you promote me to number one?
Hm?
Hmm?
Never mind.
Let's just say...
when you feel like it,
give me a kiss on the cheek...
as your answer, then.
Here.
Mm.
Tasty.
How has it been working here?
Is everything okay?
It has been exhausting but quite fun.
At first, I could not sleep well.
Once I got used to the surroundings,
I ended up barely getting any sleep either.
I have been very busy.
You have to visit the weir
with Mr. Wasin tomorrow, right?
Precisely.
Today,
I just got back from the dam.
It was a blast.
It should be the same tomorrow.
The seniors said
they would grill the fish they caught there.
Really?
Listen.
Don't get too caught up in the fun, okay?
It's dangerous here.
Wherever you go,
keep your eyes peeled,
or you might slip.
Behave yourself. Don't be naughty.
You must wear all the necessary safety equipment
and have everything prepared.
I won't be there to look after you,
so take care of yourself,
okay?
Mm.
I understand.
When you get back,
come and see me first.
There's something I want to talk to you about.
What is it?
Can you not just tell me?
Your heart...
Is it ready for the impact?
Mm...
Uh...
Between us,
well...
You...
Little Jam...
My feelings
have changed,
and I don't know when.
They've changed for the better, though.
Like...
I'm not joking here either.
I've been thinking about it over and over.
I've thought this through.
I like you.
Like...
I've really fallen for you.
Actually...
it's more than just "like."
You're quiet because you're shy?
Don't be.
Because I'm shy, too.
What about you?
Do you feel the same?
Oh...
Asleep...
[Your Third Series]
♫Still feeling lonely? Well, you've got me,♫
♫Keeping you busy every day♫
♫I might not be the one you wanted,♫
♫But give it time, you'll love me anyway♫
♫It's your heart, so it's your choice,♫
♫I won't ever stand in your way♫
♫But when they make you blue,♫
♫Can you please let me take care of you?♫
♫I'm here to love you as myself, not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you,
no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart, lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]
[Office]
What is it? What's going on?
I went to the orchard this morning
and saw a young man, around 20 years old.
I believe he trespassed into the orchard last night.
My guess is that he got lost and tired.
Is he an outsider or one of us?
He's probably not one of ours.
The person taking care of him says
all he does is say your name in his sleep.
After some digging around,
I believe he climbed the guardhouse.
Sarm...
Sarm!
I missed you.
Lantao.
Sit down.
Sit down for a minute.
What has gotten into you,
climbing the fence like that?
Why didn't you just come in properly?
Now that's the real Sarm talking.
Huh?
I missed you so much.
Doing it the normal way isn't memorable, Sarm.
I want to leave an unforgettable impression on you.
And how did that go?
Hm?
Was it worth it?
Your legs almost got hurt, didn't they?
It was worth it just to see you.
Does your dad know you came here?
Don't tell me you ran away from him?
He knew,
and he didn't mind.
You left something behind on Ko Pha-ngan,
and I'm here to return it to you.
Left?
Left what?
You left your heart with me back on the island.
You went home without even saying goodbye to me.
And now I'm at fault
for coming to find my own heart?
Did you find it?
I did.
My beating heart
is right in front of me.
What did the doctor say?
The initial examination
found no bruises or wounds.
But the heart is missing a caretaker.
Can you be serious for a moment?
Hm?
Look at me, okay?
I'm not playing.
Fine!
The doctor said I was simply exhausted
and told me to rest up for a bit.
Please, just don't kick me out.
I've already decided that
I'm staying here.
Staying here?
Yes!
Oh?
Please let me work with you.
I can do everything.
You already knew I could climb the guardhouse.
Your dozens of guards
couldn't even catch me.
I'm pretty good at sneaking around, you know.
Lantao.
How about this?
Once you've recovered,
we'll talk about it.
Your hand's so warm, Sarm.
I have to go to work now.
No.
I don't wanna be alone.
Sarm,
please stay with me.
Sarm?!
Why are there two of you?
What do you think?
It's good that you're here.
Take care of him for me.
And don't tease him too much, either.
I'm begging you.
Sure.
Go enjoy paying the price for
abandoning your work for six months.
Also...
Come have dinner at the main house.
Dad's missing you.
Mm.
Please no!
- Sarm!
- Kiddo.
Sarm.
Hey, Lantao!
Why are you so strong?
I have to go now.
Go on.
Little boy.
Have a seat.
Sarm has a ton of work ahead of him.
No, I refuse to listen!
Will you listen to me?
No!
You're a bad boy, aren't you?
Not listening!
What will the bad boy get?
Don't know!
- Here's your flick.
- Ow!
Ah!
Whoa!
Gosh, Song, you jerk!
I told you not to tease him.
Who's that kid?
Oh, that's Mr. Jam.
He's Mr. Sib's man.
Mr. Sib's man?
Correct.
Is he having a secret affair?
It's not like that.
Uh, well...
Mr. Jam is his assistant.
His assistant?
Yes, his assistant.
You can go back alone, right?
A piece of cake, Wasin.
Very well.
Let's have a meal with the workers, then.
Right.
Let's go.
- Hey!
- Whoa!
- Jam! Be careful!
- Mr. Jam!
Mind your legs.
Are you alright, Mr. Jam?
Where does it hurt?
My foot hurts.
We need to take him to the medical center, Mr. Thee.
I'll take him there.
You're new here, so I guess you don't know who I am.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Thee,
a caretaker here.
I am Jam...
Jiranat,
and I am Mr. Sib's assistant.
Once you get home,
try not to use your hand too much,
or it might swell and ache.
Right.
Jam.
Excuse me for a moment.
Okay.
Which worker's quarters are you staying in, Jam?
I'll call a ride to take you there.
And once you're there,
don't forget to take the medicine.
Understood.
I'll go and prescribe the medicine for you.
Wait a moment, okay?
- Okay.
- Alright.
- Hey Little Jam!
- Whoa, Mr. Sarm?!
- Little Jam!
- How did you get here?
Ow...
Ow! Hey!
Let go of me first.
Jam.
Aww!
Are you hurt?
Gosh...
Little Jam!
I've heard from the workers
that you slipped and fell over,
broke all your limbs,
and split your head open!
- You...
- Does it hurt a lot?
Don't worry, though.
That stream,
it's getting buried.
You got hurt by it, so it deserves to disappear.
Do not overreact.
I am fine, actually.
Gosh...
What did you do to slip?
I was simply being careless.
Oh, Little Jam...
Come on.
Let's go home.
I'm here to pick you up.
Mm.
Let's go.
Here.
Take it slow.
Oh, oh.
Oh, be careful.
Here, here.
Ow...
- Take it slow, okay?
- Right.
Slowly.
Gently.
Oh.
Slowly.
Gently now.
Are you okay? Take it slow.
Where did the patient in this bed go?
It seems...
Jam has already gone home.
He already went home?
Yes.
This is not the way back to my worker's quarters.
Who says you have to go back and live alone?
You're staying with me.
But I want to go back to my quarters.
Listen.
Your hand and leg hurt this much.
How can you go back to living alone?
But...
How about this?
It's your choice:
me living with you,
or you living with me.
Decide.
Why are you threatening me?
Mm.
Don't change the topic.
What will it be?
You're taking forever here.
The decision is mine, then.
You're staying with me.
Fine, I guess.
Now then,
where are my lovely children?
Mr. Song declines the dinner invitation,
saying he's on a diet.
As for Mr. Sarm, he recently informed us that
he has a life-or-death matter to attend to.
So he probably won't be joining dinner either.
Can't they all just give me a break?
So this means...
I have to sit here and eat all alone,
hm?
From the looks of it,
it appears so, unfortunately.
The children are starting to keep secrets
and act all suspicious.
They're just like their father.
Hey.
Yes?
Are you talking to a ghost or something?
I can hear
your intrusive thoughts!
Nothing.
By the way...
did Sarm tell you where he's off to?
The reason he gave me was that
he had to take care of Mr. Jam
- after his accident.
- Mm, mm.
Sounds familiar.
I feel like I've heard that name before.
Oh.
Well...
He's the one who brought Mr. Sarm back from the island.
Sib's man?
Then...
What does his accident have to do with Sarm,
huh?
I'm afraid I don't know about that either.
Just go.
- Play me ten songs or so.
- Right away.
Until my migraine is gone.
Mr. Sarm,
I forgot my shirt and towel.
Can you grab them for me?
Mr. Sarm?
Sarm...
Yes?
Can you grab me my shirt and towel, please?
I forgot to bring them with me.
Mm...
You...
Little Jam.
Who...
did you ask to grab the stuff for you?
Sarm, of course.
I asked you to grab them for me, Sarm.
Who?
Sarm, obviously.
No problem.
Mm...
Keep calling me that.
You'll get used to it.
Wash up properly, alright?
Come to think of it...
Mr. Sarm does know how to make sense when he talks.
I think...
I am starting to figure him out.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Wake up!
Get up!
Whoa!
So?
You told me to wake you up early, didn't you?
Hm?
It's getting late.
Oh...
Slept soundly, huh?
Why do you want to get up so early?
Where are you going?
Hm?
Where?
To work, obviously.
I have so many things to deal with.
Take a day off.
You're not fully recovered.
How could I?
You would not understand, Mr. Sarm.
"Mr. Sarm" again.
Well, I want to call you "Mr. Sarm."
Fine.
If that's what you want to call me,
then replace "a-r-m" with "p-o-u-s-e" instead.
What is it,
Mr. S-pouse?
- Yes, what is it, dear?
- Hey.
I did not call you that.
Keep calling me that. You'll get used to it.
Mr. Spouse.
Mr. Spouse, Mr. Spouse.
Mr. Sarm.
Mr. Sarm again?
It's "Mr. Spouse."
Mr. Spouse.
Mr. Spouse, Mr. Spouse.
Are you not working today?
I am, but how can I?
I'm waiting to get the kitten's wounds cleaned.
I am not a cat.
Oh, right.
You're not a cat.
With such ferocity,
you're basically a mighty tiger.
With a hint of a wild bull.
Mr. Sarm!
Just kidding.
Don't get mad, please.
Okay, I'll stop.
Hey.
Go take a shower already
so you can have breakfast.
For today's breakfast...
I'm the one doing the cooking.
Come on.
Right.
Ow...
Need a lift?
It is okay.
Just your hand will do.
Sure thing.
My left hand,
or my right hand?
My right hand?
Oh, oh, oh.
Better put it down.
Just kidding.
A hand, then.
Oh, oh.
Are you sure you can walk?
Yes.
Let's go.
Oh, here, here.
It's like you've got a broken leg.
Today's breakfast is
shiitake mushroom porridge.
Smells wonderful.
Served with giant deep-fried crab meat rolls...
Ha!
Along with steamed enoki mushrooms in soy sauce.
And the most important dish of all...
stir-fried flower crab with black pepper...
All prepared by...
yours truly.
Please enjoy.
Never knew you could cook.
They're all delicious.
Try them.
Which one is the tastiest?
The tastiest one...
is me, of course.
I'm the tastiest.
Mm.
It really does taste good.
Ha-ha, I knew it.
If you enjoy the food, you have to come and see me
so you can enjoy it more often.
You talk as if you are not busy.
I see you come home
exhausted every day, all wet and dirty.
For you, Little Jam,
you're always my first priority.
Not only can I cook,
but I can do it all,
fixing electrical faults
or even burst water pipes.
Oh...
Oh.
Oh!
You're sore?
I can give you a massage.
If you're stressed out,
I can crack some jokes for you.
Ha-ha!
Or if you want to go somewhere,
even on a long trip,
I can take you there
no matter how far it is.
Or if you want to
rest on my shoulder,
be my guest.
If you want a warm hug,
I'm happy to give you one.
I take better care of you
than any insurance company could.
I can give you advice on anything.
I never slack on external affairs,
nor do I ease up on internal matters.
Because this is me, Sarm. Who else could it be?
Happy.
Yes?
I flirted,
threw countless hints,
and served myself on a silver platter,
yet he still didn't get it.
Or do I have to spell it out
and say, "I love you, kiddo"?!
Oh...
I've become shy.
All I can do is act playful,
so he thinks I'm just fooling around.
Though we're close,
it feels like there's a wall between us,
keeping us far apart.
This injury
reminds me of our time on the island.
Back then, he never left me behind,
even though he could have just tossed me into the ocean.
Part of me feels delighted,
yet the other part tells me to stay away
and not fall for him any further.
Mr. Sarm loves making me feel things,
but I won't budge.
He loves playing with my heart,
but I won't bite.
Whatever it might be,
you must stay at my place.
I am not that injured.
I can take care of myself.
I accept no objections.
No.
I cannot sleep well at your place.
Looking all bitter.
Am I really not allowed to disagree?
I did not do anything.
What do I have to do for you to be okay?
I want to hug Mr. Croc to sleep.
Gosh...
Okay.
You can bring him to my place.
How's it going, Ning-nong?
Hello, Sarm.
Hello.
Oh hey, what's up?
Isn't this your day off?
How can I rest?
I'm worried about them.
Right.
This one's highly sought after.
Oh. Just like its father.
So many people want to get a hold of it,
but you don't want to let it go?
Oh, the horse stays with me.
But the offers are extremely high.
They're willing to fight for it.
Money can't buy me.
Whoa...
I really respect what you stand for.
If it's below what I ask, that is.
Ow...
You seem to really love these horses, Sarm.
I, too,
want to have a horse of my own.
I do, of course.
I've been raising them since they were little.
By the way,
you're going to the orange farm?
Yes.
Can I go there with you?
Hop on, then. Come on.
Jam.
- Hello, Doctor Song.
- Hi.
It's been a long while, hasn't it?
What happened to you?
A minor accident.
Yesterday, I went to a weir with Wasin,
but I slipped on the way back.
Aww...
I guess it's a blessing in disguise, isn't it, Jam?
Why did Sarm send you
to be with those men?
Did you get messed with?
Wasin did not do anything to me.
They were all so kind.
No...
I mean, was Sarm messing with you
by making you do a task like that?
I do not think so.
I have to work with every department either way.
Working with Wasin was a lot of fun.
I got to handle all sorts of fun tasks.
Hang in there, Jam.
Come on, shall I order you some dessert?
The harder the work, the more energy you'll need, right?
Don't push yourself too much, okay?
You'll wear yourself out.
Thank you,
but I am still good to go.
"Jiranat"
means "One who cannot afford to lose."
Work isn't everything in life.
It won't do you any good if you ruin your health.
After...
you're done with dessert,
shall we ride around the farm on horseback
to unwind for a bit?
I would love to.
That's more like it.
Alright.
What do you think?
Are you starting to like it here?
I told you, it's peaceful here.
Everyone loves it.
- Whoa!
Are you okay, Ning-nong?
Sarm.
Oh, Song.
Perfect timing. Take care of him for me.
What are you doing here?
What are you all doing here?
Huh?!
Why are you here?!
Hello?
No one's going to answer my question?
Hey!
There are so many of you here.
What is it?
What are you doing here?
Is my question that difficult?
It's not like I'm asking an Olympiad-level question.
It's not!
It's dead simple!
What are you doing?!
Huh?!
What would you do if our visitors got scared of you?
What the hell?
Why is no one answering me?!
Little Jam is still injured.
I already told him to take a rest.
I should scold him
for being out and about like this.
Gosh, I'm passing out...
- Ah!
- Eek!
Sarm!
Mr. Sarm!
Fucking Sarm!
What should we do?
I guess we have to
give him CPR.
Three...
two...
one...
- Ow!
- Ouch!
Ning-nong, you do it.
But I'm a horse doctor.
Song, you treat people.
But I'm an aesthetic doctor.
Jam.
I am an assistant secretary.
- Please help Sarm.
- Please, Jam.
I really cannot.
Song.
Gasp!
What?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Oh...
Whoa, Mr. Sarm!
- Hey, stupid Sarm!
- Mr. Sarm!
Let's bring him inside.
Okay.
- Mr. Sarm.
- You're so fucking heavy.
Mr. Sarm...
How come my twin brother is this heavy?
Was someone going to give Sarm CPR?
I want to chime in, too!
Sarm!
Uh...
Jam, Ning-nong,
do you two know each other yet?
Did you two happen to meet while working?
Umm, we didn't, actually.
I mostly work at the horse farm
and the pet hospital.
Oh...
Then, you two should get to know each other.
I think...
you're about the same age.
Mm...
I'm Ning-nong.
I'm a vet and the caretaker for Sarm's horses.
I am Jiranat,
Sarm's housekeeper.
Alright...
Just kidding.
I am currently stationed in the engineering department.
Soon, I will probably get rotated over to the horse farm.
Nice to meet you, Doctor Ning-nong.
You can simply call me by my name.
Mm, likewise.
You can just call me by my name.
How long have you been working here?
Only a few months, actually.
Have you had khao soi at the place near the factory?
It is very good.
That sounds tasty, actually.
Do you have any restaurants
or bakeries here that you would recommend?
So I can hurry over and check in.
I actually want to try them all,
but I would need more time
since I am leaving the farm in three months.
Oh, what a shame.
Mm... there are a lot of restaurants around here.
There's a stall by the beer garden,
near the path to the waterfall.
It's my go-to.
I mostly go there...
with Sarm.
Some days, Sarm eats with me.
Other days, he takes me to other restaurants.
But the best one is
the som tam place that serves northeastern Thai food.
But...
can you eat this kind of food?
I can tell just by looking at you
that you're not familiar with them.
I have no problem with any of them.
I am not much of a fan of pla ra, though
But laab with beef blood is at the top of my list.
Suea rong hai, in particular,
is my absolute favorite.
Shall we go there together?
Jam, why not invite Sarm, too?
You should try inviting him, Doctor Ning-nong.
I'd rather not.
I don't know if he's a fan of som tam.
Mr. Sarm is not a picky eater.
He eats all sorts of dishes.
Back on the island,
he went squid fishing with Uncle Keua
and ate it raw.
Occasionally, he would also catch giant grubs
and dip them in salt to eat
while playing cards with Aunt Samrui.
Then...
I guess you should invite him.
Do you usually invite him to places?
I never invite him.
He is the one coming to me.
I did nothing.
He came to me himself.
Why am I even teasing Doctor Ning-nong?
Gosh...
I don't know.
I'm full of jealousy.
Well then, I should get going.
The farm needs me urgently.
Be seeing you.
Oh...
- See you around.
- See you.
By the way, Jam.
Aren't you worried about Sarm?
He has got more than nine lives.
Bad things rarely come his way.
What you said makes sense.
Several years ago, Sarm had a business.
But then he stepped on the local authority's toes,
so he cursed Sarm with black magic.
But Sarm was completely fine.
- Really, Song?
- Yeah.
And Mr. Sarm...
Does he pass out often?
He never passes out, actually.
This came as a surprise to me, too,
seeing him pass out for the first time.
Oh?
What's up?
Mm.
How are you?
Ouch...
I'm a little out of it.
My body feels tired,
like I don't have much energy.
Right, right.
Let me talk to the doctor real quick, okay?
Ow, ow, ow.
Gentle.
Not going to say anything?
Where does it hurt?
Ow.
Ouch...
Right here.
Ow...
It hurts here.
Ow.
Right here.
Here
and right here.
Ouch...
You are
always up late at night,
still working.
Are you going to work 24 hours a day?
You are a human, not a robot.
Know your limits.
Some nights, you are just like that neighbor
who stays up all night doing stuff.
Are you...
even listening to me?
I am.
Well, everything I say goes in one ear and out the other.
Ow...
Feel like I'm going to fall.
Little Jam.
Whoa, whoa. Hey...
Why do you not sit down first?
I will go get the doctor for you.
No need, Little Jam.
No need for the doctor.
Hugging you
right here
is enough to recharge my energy.
Soon, I'll be back on my feet
and stronger than ever.
Little Jam.
Hm?
The truth is, I...
I...
You are going to make a joke about
being the president of the company, right?
Listen, Little Jam.
I'm being serious.
I'm dead serious.
I really am.
Listen carefully, okay?
Mm.
I...
- Sarm.
- love...
Why are you here?
I didn't even summon you here.
What the hell?
Watch that foul mouth of yours, Sarm.
I'm here for Jam.
I've had him booked since 1:30 P.M.
We're having shabu-shabu at the back of the farm.
What about you?
Why are you still here?
Why don't you go home already?
My twin brother
is clearly falling in love.
I just don't know who it is.
Ning-nong?
Or is it...
Lantao?
He takes good care of so many people
that I feel like he belongs to everyone.
If I want to find out,
I'll have to find the answer myself.
Curse you, Sarm.
Shit!
He has Jam with him!
Sarm!
Damn it, Sarm...
You're going for the golden boy?
Hello, Mr. Thee.
We've met before.
There is still a lot more that I need to learn.
Please take care of me and guide me.
"Mr. Thee" sounds a bit too distant.
You can call me by my name.
It sounds far more pleasing.
If so...
allow me to call you by your name.
With pleasure.
By the way, Jam...
You owe me one.
Since when have I owed you?
You owe me a thank-you.
Well...
I want you to repay me by...
having lunch with me every day,
and with no one else.
Right.
Bye.
Jam!
Lantao, how did you get here?
I'm here to find the love of my life.
You work here?
That's right.
I work in the QC department.
No, and it's not 'cause Sarm pulled some strings.
Yesterday,
Sarm himself told me to apply for a job here.
And I got the job on my own merits.
By the way,
you work here, too, Jam?
Mm.
But I will not be here for long.
I am only here short-term.
Oh.
And where are you staying?
I am staying in the quarters in the Replica Town Zone.
Are you in a hurry to get home this evening?
Are you inviting me to go somewhere?
To have Thai BBQ.
Mm.
I am down.
Yay!
Jam,
let's make the most of tonight.
Sorry,
all the tables are taken.
What about that one?
It's already reserved.
Jam...
Do you want to sit with me?
Apparently,
my friends ditched me.
Are we bothering you, Wasin?
I just want to find Sarm.
So why does the farm have to be this vast?
Ow.
Oh...
Are you alright?
I'm gonna go look for the love of my life.
And my legs hurt.
Come here.
Ow.
Why did you slip out of the medical center?
How did you know?
It's the gown.
I didn't.
I just didn't tell anyone I'd left.
I don't want to be there anymore.
Why not?
Were the doctors being strict?
Sarm wasn't there.
Do you know where he is?
I don't really know.
It's just Wasin here,
and he's taking you back to the medical center.
Come.
Come on.
I'm not going with you.
I'm gonna go look for the love of my life.
Your legs are still hurting.
The doctors will be looking all over for you again.
I'm not going!
Oh...
Should've stayed away.
And now I've been scratched by a cat.
Why did you grab me, then?
You're a stubborn cat,
so into the basket you go.
Not at all.
Sitting here by myself
is kind of lonely.
Come on.
Well, then...
- We will join you.
- The seats are yours.
Come on.
Excuse me,
could we get some extra sets of dishes?
Make it two.
Thank you.
These are yours.
Well, well, Lantao.
Looking at me like that,
do you have a problem with me?
If you weren't looking at me,
how did you know I was?
Because I was looking at you.
Why, though?
Um...
Because you're cute, I guess?
Quit being a player, Wasin.
I hate players!
I'm no player.
I'm just looking at you.
Ew...
Don't mess with me.
I like Sarm,
and no one else.
Why do you like Mr. Sarm?
Cause he's handsome.
I like someone who's good-looking and caring.
A caring person?
What about someone who wears a helmet?
Hm?
I don't want one.
I don't like engineers.
Be careful what you hate,
because you might end up with one.
Wasin, you're talking nonsense.
Here.
This one's yours, Jam.
Why did you give this to me?
I already have one on my plate.
Here.
You're exhausted, Jam.
You've been working all day,
so you need to eat well.
What's wrong?
No, you.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to pick you up.
What is it?
Are you awake?
Gosh...
Make sure you're free this evening.
I am already occupied.
With who?
And where?
Thee invited me to a green market.
You two are close?
And I cannot be?
No.
Nothing.
I won't let you go.
Who are you
to stop me from going wherever I want?
I don't care.
I won't let you go.
Meet me in the evening.
I've got something for you to do until late.
Evenings are after work hours.
I can report this to the Ministry of Labour.
Come stand right here, Jam.
Let me take photos for you.
Right.
Okay.
Ready?
Alright.
You're glued to him, aren't you,
Thee?
You're not up to any good with Little Jam.
How dare
you lay your finger on my Little Jam?
Beautiful?
Beautiful.
As for this spot, I think...
this angle
should work.
Take a look.
Is it alright?
Let's take photos together.
Whoa!
Shit...
That was close.
- Hey!
- Whoa!
Song.
How did you get here?
And how did you get here?
No wonder...
That's why you're acting like...
a dog abandoned by its owner.
You really have a jinxing mouth.
You like Jam?
Oh, I'm way beyond that.
I love Little Jam.
I really do.
I absolutely do.
If I ripped my heart out,
it'd scream "I love Little Jam."
"I love Little Jam."
That much?
Yeah, I love him that much.
You're a doctor, so you should know
how a human heart beats.
But I don't.
Hm.
All I know is that my heart
beats like this.
"I love Little Jam."
Inhale, and it goes,
Right.
Exhale, and it goes,
"I love Little Jam."
I see you two fighting all the time.
When did you two fall in love?
Hm.
I used to be harsh in the past.
But now, I'm all about him.
You only tasted the appetizers,
but now, it's time for the main course, Little Jam.
Little Jam.
I'm coming for you.
Little Jam...
Hey, Little Jam.
I'm coming for you.
[Office]
How accurate?
Without fail.
Here goes nothing.
If it's auspicious, then I'm all ears.
If it's not, then I'll ignore his words.
What is it you wish to know?
Your business?
Health?
Love.
Whoa.
I never thought you'd actually say that yourself.
Come on.
Will my love flourish?
It certainly will,
but it will take you a while
to prove yourself.
Can you be a bit clearer?
Like...
what else do I have to prove?
Everything
depends on you,
both external
and internal.
So I have to get an internal exam?
Damn it, Sarm!
In the past,
you've met many people
and fostered relationships with all of them.
Yet those relationships remain vague and unclear.
Outsiders
see you as a player,
having all sorts of affairs.
Not true.
You're slandering me?
Shut it.
Well, it's not true.
Listen to him carefully first.
Quiet.
Right.
If you wish your love to bloom,
be direct and to the point.
Be honest with your emotions.
And above all,
keep a clear head.
Then I'll just ask you straight.
When will I get married?
The reading says that
you'll get married at the age of
35.
35?!
What?! Five more years?!
Nuts!
No way!
No, that sucks.
That's ages from now.
Are you serious?
Hold on.
A major event is about to take place
at Adisuan Farm.
You heard him.
Shit. I'm getting chills.
Yeah, it's a major event.
I literally just signed off on the budget.
Don't confess to anyone yet, okay?
I'm trying to win you over.
Are you close with Thee now?
Why do you hang out with him so much?
Well, I have been working with him lately.
If you have time, come to my place.
I keep a lot of
important things in my office.
♫Filling this heart that once felt empty inside♫
♫A charge of energy whenever I'm tired♫
♫Just having you near…♫
♫You're the positive energy in my life♫
♫Filling this heart that once felt empty inside♫
♫A charge of energy whenever I'm tired♫
♫Just having you near…♫
♫Come charge my heart for me, baby♫
♫You're walking positive energy♫
♫You charge my heart and bring me back to life♫
[Your Third Series]